# **Justin Dulay**

# Email: justin.dulay@slu.edu

I am an undergraduate student at Saint Louis University majoring in computer science with a minor in mathematics. I lead others with a level head and a friendly spirit, always open to growth and feedback. My interests lean heavily in research in machine learning and utilizing it as a medium to solve human rights problems.

# **EDUCATION**

Computer Science, B.S. / Saint Louis University, St Louis, MO

[May 2021]

- Honors Program Scholar
- Presidential Scholarship Finalist
- James Costigan Scholarship Recipient

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Research Assistant / Saint Louis University, St Louis, MO

[May 2020-Present]

• Lab Assitant to Abby Stylianou, PhD, in computer vision and deep learning to solve human rights problems.

Applications Developer Intern / Centene Corporation, St Louis, MO

[May 2019-May 2020]

- Writes microservices in Go in a highly agile environment for Centene's TruCare NextGen project, a comprehensive insurance claims and health management platform.
- Work stories from beginning to end from development and peer review to deployments in production, utilizing a microservices architecture with Go, Jenkins, and Kubernetes
- **Key Technologies:** Jenkins pipelines, Kubernetes clusters via Rancher, Docker image building and manipulation, Go development, RESTful APIs

#### President / MEDLaunch, St Louis, MO

[June 2019-Present]

• Leads a student incubator of more than 50 medical and engineering students, manages finances of the organization, and strategizes with a premier board of directors.

## ORISE Fellow / US Food and Drug Administration, St Louis, MO

[Summer 2018]

- Developed methods for chemometrics of Raman spectral data for pharmaceutical assays, including machine learning design, PCA, KNN, and PLS regression models.
- Utilized various backscattering and transmission Raman spectroscopic instruments
- Drafted a scientific publication detailing a novel method to non-destructively screen for pharmaceutical degradation in pharmaceutical compounding facilities

## **RELEVANT SKILLS**

 Agile, C/C++, Computer Vision, Confidential US Security Clearance, Data Science, Deep Learning, DevOps, Docker, Jenkins, Go, Linear Algebra, Machine Learning, Microservices, MongoDB, Project Management, Python, PyTorch, React Native, Research, Swift, SQL